(Bernadette:)She's just excited
about the holidays.
(Sheldon:)Yes, and she's not taking
my feelings into account at all.
(Sheldon:)Maybe it's time
I teach her a lesson.
(Bernadette:)How?
(Sheldon:)Hmm. It'd have
to be something heinous,
(Sheldon:)something that makes her
as miserable as she's making me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I've got it.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)This is good.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)I'm going to buy her a present.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, you're gonna
have to walk me through that.
(Sheldon:)With gift-giving, there's
an implied social contract.
(Sheldon:)If I show up
(Sheldon:)tonight with a present,
and she doesn't have one for me,
(Sheldon:)she'll feel terrible.
(Bernadette:)Then you're both sad?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Maybe she'll feel so guilty,
(Sheldon:)she'll never make me celebrate
the holidays again.
(Bernadette:)So your evil plot here is to buy
your girlfriend a present?
(Sheldon:)That's right.
(Sheldon:)So stay on my good side, or I'll
get you a little something, too.